[Music]
today we're going to take a look at how
to install and remove feather hair
extensions there's a few different
methods and tools for doing this I'm
going to be using the salon toolkit
available here at Moonlight feather.
comom when using multiple feathers I
like to crimp them together into one
bead first and then leave about half an
inch exposed but if you're just putting
in one Fe you can skip this stuff the
hair and hold it out of the way with a
clip I'll start by choosing the location
to put the extension we want to make
sure there's enough hair to cover the
crimp bead when we're done choose a bead
to match your hair color and thread it
on the
[Music]
needle hook a small lock of hair with
the needle and put it back through the
bead I let the bead sit about half an
inch away from my
[Music]
scalp I hold hold the bead tight against
my thumb using the hair using the
feathers I trimmed together previously
insert the free ends into the second
bead this is where a mirror can come in
really handy before you crimp the bead
be sure to hold the hair and feather
against your scalp as they would lay
naturally crimp the beads with the
pliers and you're
done feathers can be shampooed curled
and straightened just be careful you
don't snag them with your comb and they
can last for months but if they do break
then just clip off the damaged end and
you can reattach
[Music]
it to remove the extensions insert the
tips of the removing tool into the
closed hole of the bead and squeeze the
beads will open and the feathers will
slide right off but don't reuse the
beads after the first use they won't
have as much holding power and the
extensions will slide right
off and now your feathers are ready hope
you enjoy them
[Music]